



Helsinki, Finland



(+358) 044 0303 407



matiasnie2@gmail.com



matiasnieminen.fi



MATIAS NIEMINEN

I'm a 23-year-old computer science student from the University of Helsinki, currently in my second year of studies. As of now, I am concentrating on full stack development, but my studies will branch out to leadership and business management as well.

My current programming repertoire includes languages such as Java, C#, Javascript (Node.js, React.js, Express, MongoDB), SQL, and Python. I enjoy learning new languages and indulging in software projects in my free time, which gives me an edge in swift improvement.

EXPERIENCE

Jun 2017 — Jul 2021

Web developer • Contract • Student Union of the University of Jyväskylä

Jun 2017 — Mar 2020

Receptionist • Part-time • Scandic Hotels Oy

Jun 2017 — Mar 2020

Waiter • Part-time • Scandic Hotels Oy

EDUCATION

Sep 2021 — May 2023

University of Helsinki, Helsinki

• Bachelor's degree in Computer science

Sep 2014 — May 2017

Tampereen seudun ammattiopisto Tredu, Tampere

• Degree in hospitality, secondary education

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Finnish: C2 (Native)
English: C1 (Advanced)
Russian: A2 (Elementary)